Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
They caught the betrayer!
Wow Dundar Bey.
It turns out you are the betrayer huh?
Betrayer!
Murderer! Murderer! You killed my son!
My son died because of you!
Look at my face! How could you do that
to my son? How could you?!
I will kill you!
I will choke you with my bare hands!
Do you hear me? I will kill you
with my bare hands
You killed my son!
You'll pay for this!
Suleiman Shah...
Great Suleiman Shah's son...
Now look at him.
It's over.
Ev.. ever... everything is over.
They caught him.
You couldn't...
be a proper Bey, Dundar Bey!
You led us to the cliff!
Suleiman shah's son...
Ertugrul Ghazi's brother...
The experienced Kayı Bey...
Dundar Bey.
You betrayed...
your own Bey...
your own breed...
your own tent,
your own religion brothers and sisters.
Now tell us every single thing.
I wanted Kayıs...
I wanted Kayıs to be good.
I wanted these wars which
waste our children...
to end.
Are you telling me that you told our
plans to the enemy and...
led us to their ambushes in order to
keep us safe, huh?
Tell me!
We were going to give
a few martyrs...
but we would have saved the whole
community.
At the cost of Bayhoca's blood, ha?
At the cost of Bayhoca's blood ha?
Savcı Bey!
You shall sit down.
I didn't do it on purpose of
getting Bayhoca killed.
My intention was not that.
With whom did you collaborated...
to kill Kayı Bey?
Tell me.
With all the enemies of Kayıs.
Isn't this true Dündar!?
Bring them.
Here...
Here are your brothers.
Here are your fellows.
Now tell me.
We were in touch with Nicola.
Louder!
This was your first chance.
You told everything to Nicola.
He knew every step of ours!
Anything else?
They wanted to get the housing documents.
They wanted to disgrace you.
We planned the Commander's arrival
to the tent with these two.
This was your second chance.
You let the infidel disgrace our tribe!
Anything else?
I worked with Togay, too.
This was...
your third chance!
You worked with infidel Papa,
infidel Constantinie...
and infidel Mongols!
Now tell me. Is there any infidel
left you didn't work with?
If your intention was good...
you wouldn't have done such things...
You cannot work withthe devil and...
claim that your intention was good.
You cannot spread Islam...
while working with the infidel!
You betrayed your Bey, your tent,
your community...
and your religion!
The penalty for this...
is death.
Pray for the last time.
Then I'll kill you
Thank you nephew.
Take all three of them.
Betrayer! Betrayer!
Don't throw anything!
Dündar!
Stop Hazal Hatun!
Dündar!!!
How could you do this to us.
You warned me, but I didn't listen to
you, Hatun.
You have nothing to do with this.
You are innocent.
Don't be afraid, nothing bad will
happen to you.
- Don't cry.
- No, no, no.
Go now.
It's enough Hazal Hatun.
Alps! Keep Hazal Hatun in the tent!
Go now!
Let's go!
Clear the way!
Aygül, don't.
Don't make it harder.
Boran, get out of the way.
I have something to tell him.
Sister.
Let me freshen up my heart.
Boran Alp, can I stay alone with my
daughter?
Father.
Daughter.
I am not your daughter.
You were my father when you made
me marry to Alisar by force!
You were my father when you caused
my brother's death with your faults!
You were my father even when you
married to my mother's murderer!
But now you are not my father!
You are a betrayer!
- Aygül, Aygül...
- You are a betrayer, you are a betrayer!
You...
- Daughter...
- I am not your daughter!
You betrayed our tribe!
You deserved to die!
I am not your daughter!
Aygül.
Daughter.
Ah, daughter.
Forgive your father, daughter.
forgive me.
They went... they went silent.
Osman must be talking with Beys
about how they'll kill Dundar.
The betrayal is visible now.
The betrayer accepted the accusations.
The tradition is clear.
Dundar Bey must be...
executed without any delay.
I want to do it Osman Bey.
Pass it on me.
Brother...
this is not an individual issue.
This concerns the whole Kayı Tribe.
Alps will...
do the execution.
According to tradition...
He'll be choked by bow string.
Savcı my son, everybody suffered.
Each family has a martyr.
Let them end him...
so his greed shall go under soil.
This is going to be done with sunrise.
What are we going to do with
Dundar Bey's wealth, my Bey?
The betrayer's wealth is given away
to the community.
What about Hazal Hatun?
She's going to get her share.
Not much, not less, just her share.
Aygül...
She is a daughter of a Bey, Osman Bey.
She should also have her share.
Isn't she going to get her share
from her father's wealth?
Also, her son Kayı Alp should
get his share
Everyone will get their share.
The rules of the religion are clear.
We'll take over the undeserved gain.
Aygül is my sister.
She is my precious one.
She doesn't need the wealth which
was gained unfairly.
After she gets her share...
I'll be responsible for her well being.
Eyvallah (okay) Osman Bey.
Okay then sons, these days will pass.
These days will pass.
Osman Bey.
Send Hazal Hatun to his father's.
To his brother Yavlak Arslan.
This is your duty Bala Hatun.
Do not let her get away with
any of the orphans' share.
Don't worry my Bey.
I'll do what is necessary.
Lord Nicola betrayed not only you,
but also Geyhatu.
Nicola has a venomous tongue just like
a snkae has a venomous tooth.
I'll make him eat his own tongue.
No doubts, Togay.
Now, a new duty is waiting for you.
Geyhatu's duties haven't finished.
Geyhatu himself assagined you
this new duty.
Han of the Hans Geyhatu wants me to
collect the taxes...
that Lords didn't pay to Seljuqs.
Our herds perished after the epidemic.
We need more taxes to gain strenght...
and we need more sheep and cows that
are healthy, protected from the epidcemic.
Or our state will be in a trouble.
Osman.
Isn't he a bigger threat?
This is why I am giving you
more authorization.
I will send you huge armies under
your command.
You'll collect taxes from Turkish tents
and all the Lords.
You'll crush those who don't pay!
Now go and come back
with caravans loaded gold to the gills!
Osman's and Nicola's heads are
already yours!
The archers in Yarhisar and Bilecik
are going to...
attack simultaneously.
How are they going to get out
of there ailve? They'll die!
You may be right.
Our soldiers will attack bravely,
and die as a hero, Kalanoz.
And that way, they'll be awarded
with the heaven of Jesus.
This will save us time. Isn't it worth to
sacrifice soldiers for such a great victory?
It surely does.
You are learning politics, Kalanoz.
Helen?
It's like your body is soul-free.
You are pale.
- Dündar escaped.
- How can he?!
He killed one of our soldiers
and dressed as him, then escaped.
The gold is gone!
We need the gold!
Damn the gold!
Tunnels!
Dundar didn't know about tunnels.
Osman learned I killed potter Idris.
- What else did he learn?
- Isn't this enough?
Did he find out about Petrus?
He just catched me so far.
- Do you think he knows about the tunnels?
- I am not sure.
Let me talk to Dundar. Let's see what
I am going to get out of his mouth.
Melik.
Melik was the one who saw Dundar
for the last time.
Helen go to Sogut at once.
See Melik and get information.
Now.
Yes sir.
It's a miracle that we're still alive!
We have to live until
we complete our duty.
Do not forget this.
Petrus!
Do you think Osman will let us live
as he promised, huh?
He wants to use us to the end.
We did what we could!
The last thing he's going to get
from us is our lives!
What else can we do?
Don't be so sure.
What else can he learn from us?
Tunnels.
You're not taking anything you
didn't deserve.
So you are the Hatun now, huh?
Are you still talking?
Do you want to get yourself killed?
Aygül stop.
Let her piss off.
If it wasn't for Osman Bey, I'd kill
her myself.
Come Lena, come.
You are missing the feast!
You must be praying because you didn't
end like your husband!
You wouldn't live if you were
not a Hatun.
Let go of me Bala!
- Lena!
- Let go of me Bala!
Lena stop!
- Lena!
- Osman Bey has an order.
None of you can harm me.
We are not done yet, Hazal Hatun!
Aygül!
You'll see me everytimeyou breath!
I'll make you pay for my mother
sooner or later!
Aygül!
I'll kill you if she doesn't!
Do you hear me!
Hatuns!
Stop!
Pull yourselves together!
All of these was going to be yours
when your father and I was dead.
Now you'll watch this is being
given to others.
These were yours.
I'd prefer being hungry...
to having haram(unlawful) wealth.
Alps.
Take this away.
You can take your share and leave.
Let's go.
Knowing that I won't see you again...
knowing that I won't see your
faces again...
is more important than the gold
you've taken.
If you see us again, you'll not only
lose your gold.
You should know that.
Let's go.
Valiant Dundar Bey.
So you were booed in your own tent.
You disgraced yourself in front of
kids and everyone.
So you are here.
You are here.
I'm going to death's door, right sons?
What about Hazal Hatun?
You'll learn.
Let's go.
They'll kill Dündar, then it
will be our turn.
I told you.
Osman is not done with us yet.
Osman doesn't know about tunnels.
Dundar doesn't know either.
Osman will be informed sooner or later.
What are we going to do then?
Are we going to keep on
serving Osman?
Are we going to tell him everything?
run with the hare and hunt with
the hounds. Our first mission...
is not meeting our father in heaven.
Our first mission is to send Osman
in hell!
Do not forget it Simon!
Never!
Why isn't there anyone?
Did you want to say your last
words to the community?
No one wants to see your body.
Come here, wait!
Go inside!
Daughter.
May Allah bless you.
I wish you died with your honor.
Only at that time I could say
may Allah bless you.
The arrow sticked in my son's heart!
When we found the betrayer in the
tribe with Lena...
I wish this arrow had hit your heart!
I wish that!
I wish I could be as strong as to
seek forgiveness from you.
I wish I could.
You are the disgrace of...
Kayı Tribe.
You are My grandfather Suleiman Shah's...
My father Ertugrul Ghazi's shame...
You are our broken heart.
Your death is not going to kill
our pain...
or relieve our hearts.
In return of all the pain...
This won't be enough.
Boran.
Osman Bey.
I have a last wish from you.
Allow me to die by your hands.
For your grandmother
Halime Hatun...
my beautiful mother...
don't take this away from me.
I don't deserve to be strangled
like an honorable bey.
Don't give me this honor.
That arrow which took Bayhoca's
life...
should take mine as well.
Is this your last word?
The day I took refuge in Nikola...
I saw the map of Söğüt
on the table.
They were making war plans
with Kalanoz.
There is more, my nephew.
They dug under Söğüt like
moles.
Don't lose the Söğüt that my
brother conquered to the heathens.
Don't.
Savcı Bey. Keep the word you
gave to Lena.
Osman Bey.
Give me your blessing.
Daughter...
Aygül...
May Allah forgive your sins.
I bear witness that there is no
god but Allah...
and I bear witness that Muhammad is...
the servant and Messenger of Allah.
Dündar Bey is dead.
If our agreement still stands,
let us go.
You gave your word!
You would honor our agreement!
You promised to answer all my
questions right.
So we did. We answered all your
questions correctly, Osman Bey.
What about the ones I didn't ask?
Of course, we aren't responsible
of them.
But, an agreement is an agreement.
I'll have another question.
Togay.
How did he enter the inn when he
attacked Umur Bey?
An agreement is an agreement.
You trusted me and I trusted you.
Now give me the true answer.
If you keep silent for what you know,
the agreement goes off.
There was no entrance to the inn from
the door, window, or roof.
Now tell me.
How did Togay enter the inn?
Petros?
-Tell me.
-The tunnel!
The secret tunnel that we dug from
the store to the inn.
Tunnel, huh?
How many tunnels are there?
To the church, to the macellum, and to
the inn. There are three big tunnels.
Is that so? Does Nikola know the
tunnels?
He knows it.
Come on. Let's see these tunnels.
We searched every corner
of the shop.
But even the devil would fail to find
the secret passage.
-Where does this lead to?
-Directly to the inn.
So, Togay came through here
to attack Umur Bey.
The tunnel separates into two
ways.
One to the church, other
to the macellum.
Then, Nikola would use these tunnels
to attack Söğüt.
Yes.
Kalanoz comes for this reason.
-He will attack Söğüt.
-If we hadn't found this, it'd be bad.
Not only Söğüt, Göktuğ.
They would even attack the tribe.
Now tell me, when will they attack?
-We don't know.
-We aren't informed either.
They will contact you when they attack,
will they not?
Now tell me, who will contact you?
Helen.
You have one last task to survive.
After Togay killed my brother,
trade nearly stopped.
As a shepherd, you have to feed
your herd.
If you can't, they won't listen to you.
Not only that...
they will crush you.
How? I can't even feed my soldiers.
You will provoke both your soldiers
and your merchants.
You will make them believe in the crusade
with gold and war.
I don't have the power to fight
or gold to give, Nikola!
What would happen if you
gave your tax to your soldiers...
instead of the Seljuks?
Won't Geyhatu make me pay for it?
When we take Söğüt, all the dominance
of the Turks in Bythnia will end!
Geyhatu have so much trouble that
he won't come to our borders.
Isn't that so?
And you keep talking about your
brother's vengeance!
And I talked to the emperor to convince
him to make you a lord.
-If you don't have the courage--
-Nikola!
Tell me what I can do for you,
for our victory!
Pray. You can pray for me.
And also...
I need your best archers.
-Is that all?
-That's all.
My soldiers are in your order
from tomorrow, Nikola.
May God watch over you, Yaso the Brave.
I'll take care of you right away.
Where is Dündar?
I don't know.
What did you talk about when
you visited him at the castle?
He asked me about Hazal Hatun.
Osman banished her.
-Where is Hazal now?
-With his brother at Çobanoğulları, I guess.
Dündar would probably learn this and
go after his wife already.
What about Petros?
Where is Petros?
He didn't return from İznik yet.
But he'll come tomorrow.
Why are you asking that?
Is is the big day?
The war of Söğüt...
-When?
-Tomorrow.
Good. Good. Very good.
Now, I'll tell you how you will help
our soldiers infiltrate.
We'll do what's necessary when
Petros returns tonight. Don't worry.
Open your ears and listen to me good.
The heathens are getting bolder.
They think that we are unaware.
Now, we'll talk about the measures we'll
take and the blows we'll strike.
Osman Bey, we need to stop Nikola's
soldiers before entering the tunnels.
We can strike them with a sudden
raid and evade the danger.
After all, if they enter the tunnel, we
can't know who kills who in chaos.
Thank you, Bamsı Bey. I don't want
them in Söğüt.
We can hurt Nikola's army well if we
attack them in the open with our cavalry.
We killed the traitor in the tribe but
we should be careful.
It might be false news.
Osman Bey, what say you?
What's on your mind?
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come.
My bey, Melik returned, has important news.
-Let him come.
-Tell me what you heard.
-Helen.
She came to the store.
They'll attack tomorrow.
There is little time.
-How will they attack?
-A part of the soldiers...
will enter through the tunnels.
Kalanos will attack at the gates
of Söğüt.
Tomorrow, we'll know if you lied
to us or not.
Osman Bey, a lie that will
last until tomorow...
can do me no good.
Göktuğ. Take him away.
Both Kalanos and Nikola.
Both from the tunnels and
the city gates.
In such a short time, how will we
defend both, Osman Bey?
Bamsı Bey, what would my father
Ertuğrul Ghazi say?
He would say that a game set so easy
is difficult to break.
But it is easy to break a game
that is set too difficult.
This...
This will be a difficult game.
Osman Bey is free from the hump
on his back.
He finally killed the traitor
in his tribe.
Thank Allah. Now, Osman Bey will stand
stronger against the heathens.
Not only against the heathens but
also against us.
Isn't that what we wanted? A strong ally
that we can trust.
Of course, but don't forget that...
as Osman Bey gets stronger, his
demands will grow.
Now, we need to do something big.
We should so that he'll understand that
Kızılbeyoğulları isn't an easy game.
What's on your mind, my bey father?
I will send a new caravan to İnegöl.
We'll infiltrate the grooms to the castle!
-Not yet, Malhun. Not yet.
For now, our trade should continue.
We should gain Nikola's trust as
much as possible.
So that he won't be suspicious
of anything.
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come!
My bey, Osman Bey wants to speak.
He invites you to his tent.
Here, he'll start counting
his demands.
-What will we do, my bey?
-Go and find out what he wants.
As you order, my bey.
There will be no one but the guard
alps in the tribe.
We'll strike our last blow with
the raid on the tribe.
It's time to avenge my brother!
Nikola?
Are you still troubled.
Something is wrong. I can see it.
I won't feel relieved before Helen comes.
Helen?
Tell me you have good news.
-Everything is fine, Nikola.
-What did Melik talk about with Dündar?
They talked about Hazal. Osman sent
Dündar's wife to her brother.
-That's probably where Dündar goes.
-Good. I would like him stay in Kastamonu.
So that he can work for me when
the time comes.
Helen, what about the tunnels?
Do they know what to do?
I told them what to do when the time
comes. They are as impatient as us.
They are still after the settling
documents.
After what I will do, there won't be a
single Turk left in these lands.
Not a single Turk.
-May I enter, Osman Bey?
-Come.
-Welcome, Malhun Hatun.
-Thank you, Osman Bey. Father sent regards.
-He couldn't come because he was busy.
-Aleikum Salam.
I know what he is busy with.
You are preparing a new caravan to
sent Nikola.
Don't worry, Osman Bey. We aren't
selling horses to Nikola.
I know that. That's not why
I invited you.
-Here.
-Allah bless you.
What is Osman Bey talking to
that woman?
Who knows, Bala? Maybe they did something
bad and he is questioning him.
-Here.
-Allah bless you.
This woman will bring such trouble that...
we'll miss Dündar Bey.
-Here.
-Allah bless you.
You were faultier at that...
but it was corrected.
You were faultier to hide
the thumb ring too...
but it was also corrected.
Now, there is a chance to redeem
the mistakes.
I want you to lead the caravan
to İnegöl.
Have you started to trust me, Osman Bey?
Trust can't be broken twice, you said.
Don't break my trust.
I'm happy to see you haven't forgotten it.
Continue before forgetting yours.
There is something very valuable that
I want you to bring from İnegöl.
I avenged our warriors, Togay.
-What about Kalanoz?
-He ran away.
Osman slaughtered his army.
Then I slaughtered what was left.
Geyhatu made you the Noyan
of the borders.
We are ready to die for revenge,
for you, Togay.
Revenge will wait for a while.
Firstly, we'll go after the taxes that
lords should pay to Seljuks.
We'll start with the lord of Yarhisar.
The Emperor appointed his brother Yaso in
the place of the lord I killed.
He left the castle to hunt.
If he is hunting...
let's claw him there.
With the name of Allah.
Mashallah. Mashallah.
Allah bless you.
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam, Kumral Abdal.
Kumral Abdal, I've been giving out food for
hours but there still are so many. Weird.
Pehlivan Dervish, Akça Dervish decreases
it and Sheikh Edebali increases it.
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam, Osman Bey.
Kumral Abdal.
I want to see Sheikh Edebali.
Who wouldn't, Osman Bey?
You gave me peace in my
most difficult times.
Don't you worry about losing
your place in me.
Your heart is wide, Osman Bey.
We aren't afraid.
-Come.
-Thank you.
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam.
With the name of Allah.
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam, Osman Bey.
Come.
My Sheikh.
My uncle...
my father's brother...
How could my uncle do such a thing?
Dündar Bey was a good trader,
was he not, Osman Bey?
True. True, my sheikh.
Who else's uncle was
also a trader?
Do you remember someone who
was insulted by his uncle?
His uncle was putting tripe
next to his door.
He would stone his house.
He would leave him hungry.
Who had suffered such an uncle, Osman Bey?
Our prophet, may he rest in peace.
It's our prophet. And his uncle is the
one...
who was cursed in Qur-an,
Ebu Leheb.
So, what did our prophet do?
He kept patient and continued
in his path.
He was patient and he walked
He suffered the insults, slanders
and tyranny of his uncle Ebu Leheb...
and many other relatives he had.
But he continued on his path.
Even if you give me the sun and
the moon...
I won't return from my way, he said.
After all, that's Allah's path.
And Allah choose Muhammad Mustafa
to spread his religion...
and to teach the right way to
the people.
Is it possible to turn back from this
path, Osman Bey?
My sheikh, our prophet
didn't return.
He crowned his faith
with the victory of Islam.
As the soldiers of this cause...
we won't turn back either.
Osman Bey, of course, none of
us will put us in his place.
Not at all.
Not at all, my sheikh.
And we should know that...
none of us will have his
value for Allah.
Not at all.
But we will emulate him...
and try to be like him.
We'll be patient and be on our path,
Osman Bey.
You should consider your uncle's
treason in this way.
Thank you, my sheikh.
Thank you.
Walk as our prophet did in Allah's
cause.
That's what the people and history
expects from you.
Until my last breath,
this is my cause...
and this is my path.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Deliver the goods.
-My lady, where are we going?
-Be patient. Let's find it.
What will we find?
We already found it.
My lady, what's there?
Now, listen to me well.
Finally, let's see you, pig.
We have a feast tonight.
Mongols!
How could that be?
I swear that I hit a pig!
I'm the lord of Yarhisar.
Who are you? What do you want?
-Who are you?
-Togay.
I'm Togay the Dark Shaman,
border Noyan of Geyhatu.
I heard that Osman killed your poor
brother.
You protected his throne.
May spirits protect him.
Thank you, Togay.
What do you want from me?
You delayed your tax
for the Seljuks.
Seljuks means Geyhatu.
Don't you know that?
We had my brother's funeral.
I'm hoping that you'll be understanding.
We'll send the taxes to Konya
in a few days.
This would be great.
I don't want your father to lose...
another son after your brother.
-Be quick.
-Like I said. In a few days.
Camuha. Take out the pig from
where you hid it.
Give it to the lord.
Even though I hit it.
It will be my gift.
-Bring it.
-Did I not hit it?
It's my little gift for you.
I will never forget this goodness.
Soon, you'll die, murderer.
-Will he pay his taxes?
-No.
-He wouldn't dare.
-He trusts Nikola. He knows I killed his brother.
He couldn't even speak out of his fear.
He'll kill me at first chance.
What will we do?
We'll set an unexpected great bonfire.
The dark nights of Bhytinia will
turn into a fireball.
-I told you to not come this way.
-It's because of you!
-Idiot!
-Are you talking to me?
Let's top these idiots.
-Come on, now is the time.
-How will we open the door?
If luck smiles upon us, it won't
be too hard.
-Who are you?
-We are Umur Bey's men.
We brought the goods Lord Nikola wanted.
It's all because of him!
All because of him!
-Come here!
-It's your fault!
-Close it!
-My lady!
Tell me, what are we doing here?
Osman Bey was right.
What do you want from İnegöl Castle,
Osman Bey?
Flame barrels. Nikola hides them
in a secret place in İnegöl.
How do you know that he hides
them there?
The late Zülfikar Dervish...
prepared this before
passing away.
This will take you to the
flame barrels.
But the rest is on you.
So, you trust me this much.
I invite you to jihad.
I give you opportunity.
I want to see what you will do.
I won't make you regret that,
Osman Bey.
Thank you.
We'll take as much as we can
carry and leave.
-There are two of them. Let's kill them.
-Wait. Their corpses will be found.
Then, they'll notice that the
flame barrels are missing.
Hurry! We need help at the market.
No one will leave until the crowd
leaves.
We can't use the door.
We are stuck here.
Don't be so sure.
We will leave here.
Check the door while I open the lock.
There isn't a traitor here in
your tent anymore.
You will stop Nikola's attack and
you will protect Söğüt, my Osman Bey.
Inshallah, my Bala.
Inshallah.
May Allah help us.
However...
I'm waiting
for important news from Malhun Hatun.
What does Malhun
Hatun have to do with it?
Can I come in, Osman Bey?
Come in.
Malhun Hatun.
Mashallah.
This is what you wanted, Osman Bey.
We have taken the flame barrels
from the heathens.
Mashallah.
Malhun Hatun...
you've done an important job.
You showed
me that I was right to trust you.
Thank you.
I'm happy that you
trust me again, Osman Bey.
I want to go to my tent if you excuse me.
Of course.
Send my regards to Umur Bey.
Baysungur.
- Yes, my Bey.
- Summon the Beys.
Your command, my Bey.
My Bala.
Victory is...
ours now.
What were you doing in İnegöl?
Did I ask you to go there?
How could you do it without my permission?
My Bey...
Osman Bey...
Malhun.
Did I ask you to take the helm
of the caravan?
Did I tell you to go to İnegöl?
- Osman Bey wanted me to.
- What do you mean?
Why?
Nikola wants to kill everyone in Söğüt.
How?
They dig tunnels. They will send
soldiers to the city.
What do you have to do with this?
Osman Bey wanted me to go to İnegöl.
I gave the flame barrels to Osman Bey.
He will explode the tunnels with them.
He once charged us with betrayal.
Now, he wants our help.
You did well.
My Bey...
I want to be with Osman Bey on
that war.
Let me go with my Alps.
It's okay.
Osman Bey will understand his mistake of
keeping us apart from the wars.
When Nikola's soldiers got into
to the tunnels...
we will...
fire them...
with those flame barrels.
The tunnels that they dug themselves...
will be their graves.
Mashallah.
Mashallah...
however...
how did you take these barrels, Osman Bey?
Thanks to Malhun Hatun.
Malhun Hatun.
How could she take them?
I wanted her to do it and she brought
them from İnegöl...
no
matter how dangerous it is.
Thanks to her.
How did Malhun Hatun do that?
Sheikh Zülfikar Dervish...
told me where the barrels were hidden.
However, someone that Nikola wouldn't
suspect should have got them.
He would suspect everyone.
Mashallah.
Malhun Hatun did a huge job.
Now, we can attack Nikola with
his own weapon.
They found the right way.
Umur Bey and his tent will
make us more powerful.
Yes.
These tunnels have three exits.
This exit is near Süleyman' shop.
Melik will wait there.
He will fire the flame barrel
when we say so.
We will place our Alps on to the
other two exits.
And they will catch the heathens.
We...
will stand against Kalanoz's army.
When Nikola tries to take Söğüt...
he will lose many of his soldiers.
And the liberation of Söğüt will
make it through the İnegöl.
Until that time...
with Allah's help...
Bamsı will be able to fight
with two hands.
Inshallah.
Let's wait for tomorrow.
They have two commanders.
They are heading to İnegöl.
Nikola will conquer Söğüt.
Geyhatu will make Söğüt headquarters.
Our new headquarters will be İnegöl.
What will we do?
Let's fire the feast fire.
I will...
place it into the entrance.
You will go inside and...
fire it when I tell you so.
I will chew you if you make a mistake.
Then I will eat you.
Do you understand?
I do.
Take it.
Is it done, Göktuğ Alp?
Yes, we placed them into
the tunnels, Savcı Bey.
A flame or fire is enough for them to
become the grave of the heathens.
The fire is our anger.
Tell Osman Bey.
Commander Kalanoz.
I can't wait to be welcomed
by my own people in Söğüt.
No one will be able to stop
our army in front of the castle.
Where are Lord Yaso's archers?
Are they outside the castle?
They didn't show up, Nikola.
Sir.
Talk, soldier.
Our soldiers found this near
the castle.
What's this?
Open it.
Damn it.
This is Yaso's commander.
Did Osman do that?
Togay did this.
Bring my horse.
Bring my horse!
I sent Nikola his gift.
Please don't kill me.
Send his head too.
Can they conquer Söğüt, Togay?
The mountains, the lands and the inns...
belong to Geyhatu, right?
Osman and Nikola will understand that...
Geyhatu rules these lands.
It will be too late for them.
Come.
Cerkutay's fire is waiting for you.
Now.
My Bey.
Nikola's army is coming. They look
dreaded.
We saw many dreaded.
They...
were buried in their own hollows.
Alps!
You all know what to do!
Today is the day!
May Allah help us!
Amin!
Come on!
Sir.
- What?
- The soldiers got into the tunnels.
- The attack is about to start.
- Nice.
Honor your own name, my God!
Not us, not us.
Our victory is for you.
I won't share this honor
with anyone, Kalanoz.
You will trap Osman and his Alps
when they leave their tent.
May the honor of victory be yours, Nikola.
I just want to kill Osman and
take my brother's revenge.
Osman!
Damn it!
How does he know that we will attack?
What if he knows about the tunnels?
He would destroy them by now if he knew.
Our soldiers will head into Söğüt by the
tunnels when we are fighting here.
Soldiers!
Battle order!
- Allahu Akbar!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com